Derian Sibaja

■ derfelsib@gmail.com | in linkedin.com/in/derian-felipe

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Passionate System Engineer with 2+ years of experience in developing web applications. Developed and supported 2 web applications based on technologies as .Net, and Angular. Currently working as a Web Developer, involved in projects with React/NodeJS and SFMC applying knowledge of JS, HTML and CSS/SCSS.

EDUCATION

UNA

·Bachelor's Degree - Systems Engineering. **2015-2019**

COLEGIO TÉCNICO PROFESIONAL DE FLO-RES

- ·High School Diploma.
- ·Technical IT Support Diploma.
- •Tools for Success English Course Certificate. **#** 2014.

PROJECTS

SASDI (SISTEMA DE ADMINISTRACIÓN PARA EL DESARROLLO INFANTIL) | DEVELOPER. ♥ Heredia, San Pablo. | ∰ Feb 2017 – May 2018.

• Project developed for San Pablo's local government and IMAS (Instituto Mixto de Ayuda Social) consisting of a web tool that manages employees and children information at San Pablo's CECUDI. Based on technologies on the order of Java. JavaScript. HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Hibernate, SQL and Git.

LANGUAGES

- ·Spanish Native.
- ·English Professional Working Proficiency.

SKILLS

- ·Programming and technical: JS, React, NodeJS, CSS, HTML5, NextJS, MySQL, MongoDB, Git, AWS, SFMC/Interaction Studio, REST API, Agile methodologies.
- Creativity.
- ·Teamwork.
- Growth mindset.

EXPERIENCE

3 PILLAR GLOBAL

SOFTWARE ENGINEER.

- ## July 2022 Present.
 - Full-Stack developer based on React, NodeJS, SCSS and

ACCENTURE

PHeredia, Plaza Bratsi.

WEB DEVELOPER.

- ## August 2019 July 2022.
 - Working in a project as a front-end developer based on React, NodeJS, SCSS and Git (1+ year).
 - Email developing in Salesforce Marketing Cloud platform (interaction Studio).

INTFI

Heredia, San Antonio de Belén.

DATA SCIENTIST.

- May 2019 August 2019.
 - Statistical data analysis and process automation relying on technologies such as Python, JMP and SQL PathFinder.

INFORMATION SECURITY FULL-STACK DEVELOPER. m Dec 2018 - May 2019.

• Security tools support and development relying on technologies such as HTML5, SCSS, Angular, JS, Gulp, NPM, .Net, Framework 4.6, Windows Server 2012 R2, Web API, Entity Framework and Git.